We have an update on that hijacked plane
that was going from Dubai to Tel Aviv in
Israel and it landed in Saudi Arabia.
So, this is a developing story, but it
seems like this was a terrorist attack
or an attempted one and there [music]
was some stories. Oh, the pilots were
just fighting and that's what happened.
They were because the co-pilot actually
stabbed the captain. I don't know how he
got a knife on board. I think it's being
reported it was a pocketk knife and he
tried to seize control of the plane. The
captain, from what I'm reading, is in
critical condition. I'm not sure of his
status, but the Israelis on the plane
were like, "Nah, not today." And they
broke their way into the cockpit.
>> Isn't that insane?
>> And took control of the situation.
>> So, basically, Israel, there was a 9/11
on their hands and the people that were
basically a plane got hijacked. They had
a 9/11, like the hijackers had the plane
and people broke into the cockpit and
stopped them
>> and stabilized everything. The plane was
dropping from 30,000 ft to 15,000 ft in
a short period. It was about 30,000 ft
per minute rate
>> and they took control of the situation
and there's a lot of Israelis that were
talking to media. First off, again,
everyone is safe.
>> Everyone's alive. The plane landed in
Saudi Arabia. So, to Israeli media and
other media and they had blood, some of
them had blood on their shirt because
they were the ones that went into the
cockpit to take control of the
situation. They got the captain's blood.
Obviously, it would be on their shirt.
They were saying that there was a lot of
blood in the cockpit [music]
>> and um it was a very serious situation.
Some of them were reported saying that
they really thought that they were not
going to live. Now, there's two [music]
words about what this co-pilot was
trying to do. Some were just saying he
was just trying to do a nose dive and
crash. Some were saying he wanted to
actually crash into a building into
Israel.
>> Uh more information to follow on that. I
mean, I think that obviously like if
you're taking over an airplane,
>> like I mean, there's probably some sort
of like goal for this, right? I mean,
this is a complex procedure to do that.
I would assume was probably not just
like a random, you know, this wasn't
like a random mugging on the street.
Nobody just like accidentally, you know,
you're sitting there, you're flying to
Atlanta, and you're like, actually, you
know what? Let's fly this [__]
into a building. You know, like nobody
really does this.
The wounded captain opened the door
before he passed out. Uh [snorts]
allowing the uh passengers to stop
crashing. That's insane.
>> Know again, I'm reading everything that
I can as it's coming out, but right now
[music] this is now what most people are
reporting based off a lot of testimony,
confirmed evidence, and more or less
what happened. Obviously more
information to follow, maybe motivation,
but this changes a lot. Flights from
Arab countries like the UAE to Israel is
relatively new. Direct [music] flights,
>> they already have this
>> and this obviously is going to raise a
whole new level of concern [music] about
normalization.
>> I hate to say it, but it's just true
because then you think about, well, if
it can just take one crazy co-pilot,
what if him and the actual pilot, the
captain, were on the same board? it.
First off, I just want to say that the
heroes, the Israelis that went in and
broke the
>> Bro, if you go in there and you save the
[__] airplane from crashing like
that, that is [__] insane. Like, that
is some absolute like movie heroic [__]
right? Like, oh my god. So, yeah. And
and they saved everybody too, which is
what's insane. And uh yeah, he pulled
the yolk, I guess. So, right. Can't even
comprehend this, right? So really I mean
like I don't know exactly the co-pilot
is an Omani. So let me just go ahead and
understand this correctly.
So the pilot was like a you know a
captain is like just like some Israeli
but the co-pilot was an Omani citizen
that then decided to take over the
airplane and then randomly [__] uh do
a terrorist attack. Right.
Indian is an Omani citizen. The co-pilot
is an Omani citizen. I'm reading it from
right here. The pilot was Indian. Oh,
excuse me. So, it was an Indian pilot.
His co-pilot was an Omani and the Omani
stabbed the Indian and then tried to fly
the plane into maybe a building or
something. Is that am I getting this
correct?
way into the cockpit. Even the captain,
I there's some reports saying he tried
to stop the co-pilot and maybe that's
when he stabbed him. I'm not really
sure, but that those little differences,
if they're true, I mean, that's the
difference between us reading one news
report and everyone is safe news report.
>> So, I'll get more information out as we
get it, but that's what I got so far.
>> That is ridiculous. This is going to
change things in the Middle East and
normalization with Arab countries. I
mean, realistically, let me see. Can I
pull if there's any more of this that's
going on? Uh, I have no idea. This is
some other [__] Okay, so
Omani pilot tried to hijack a plane
bound to Tel Aviv by stabbing an Indian
pilot, but the Indian pilot resisted and
with the help of two Israeli passenger
pilots landed the plane safely. Now,
compare this news to how MSM reports and
you'd think that you aren't being
brainwashed. So, this is how the media
has reported this situation. They said a
violent a quote violent altercation
between two pilots caused a flight Dubai
aircraft traveling from Saudi Arabia to
Tel Aviv to divert to Saudi Arabia.
Sources have told CNN two pilots were
wounded after they reportedly fought on
board the plane and were flying towards
Dubai and Tel Aviv, which was forced to
make an emergency landing in Saudi
Arabia. Flight from Dubai to Tel Aviv
lands quote safely in Saudi Arabia after
quote brawl between pilots. And breaking
news, a plane between Dubai and Israel
was diverted after an altercation
between a pilot and co-pilot. Israeli
officials said an Israelbound flight
made an emergency landing after an
apparent struggle in the cockpit that
left both pilots injured. Like this is,
by the way, I want to let you guys know
um this is all covered in the big plan.
It is. This is covered.
This is We can We can We can make this
stop.
We can
We can make this stop.
And I just I don't want you to never
blackpill.
Never black pill because keep in mind
when the Wall Street Journal become
leftwing, this isn't leftwing. This is
like literal um terrorist whitewashing.
That's what they're doing. like leftwing
is like saying that unions need to have
more support and Congress should listen
to these workers unions more about
providing protections for AI because
they might lose their jobs, right? Like
that's leftwing. This is literal
terrorist uh obfuscation. Like this is a
very very big difference here. Okay.
Like so uh propaganda at its finest. I
know. So Wall Street Journal has been
leftist for a long time now. After 2020
it was lost. Do you know Israel had
airplanes ready to intercept in case
this has gone wrong? Well, yeah, because
they they they're being attacked by
terrorist countries constantly, right? I
mean, Iran has like multiple terror
cells that are attacking Israel from
different directions. So, obviously,
Israel is going to have a thousand
countermeasures for this because they
have to. So, I mean, it just makes
sense. Harrowing footage and this is I
don't know how much of this I can show.
I'm going to pause if it gets brutal.
Right. So, these are the people that are
on the flight to Dubai, uh, from Dubai
to Israel that was hijacked by its own
pilot. Here we go.
Man,
that's scary, right? Nose dive. Yep.
Mhm.
>> [__] heroes on that plane. Yeah, I
know.
>> I'm from Israel with the guy saying it's
all okay. Nothing happened. We're fine.
>> Yeah. Try to calm people down.
>> Can you imagine like while all this is
happening, they're up there like [__]
fighting for the cockpit? Oh my god.
>> The plane descended 2,000 ft in seconds.
This is safe to watch. Okay, I'm going
to find it in just a second.
>> Look at this.
>> Oh my god.
Sit down. Sit down. Sit down.
>> MSM will downplay every terrorist attack
than the West. That's true. And uh
again, like let me let me go and show
you a few of these here. This is insane.
And so here's another Russian UK a
Russian and a Ukrainian saved the day.
It turns out that a Ukrainian and a
Russian pilot [snorts] wouldn't have
expected this. Uh were on board on the
Fly Dubai plane. They got a lot of
experience flying drones, right? So
plane can't be that much different. Both
could took control of the plane and
landed it after the second pilot
attacked the captain. Both pilots were
flying as regular passengers in civilian
clothes. After the incident, they
replaced the crew in the cockpit and
landed the plane. Oh my god.
>> Holy [__]
Can you imagine how the world would have
reacted if it happened? Yeah, they would
have immediately just blamed Israel.
>> The thing also is like I don't know if
this person has any connections to a
terrorist organization or it's just one
crazy person, right?
>> I think all this is still
>> it's all being revealed over time.
[screaming]
>> Turning down a little bit. It's kind of
loud. probably because everybody's
screaming because they're worried
they're about to die. Probably it
happened. Uh Netanyahu would win his
election in two weeks.
>> The secondary pilots were British. One
of the survivors interviewed on Channel
12, they said they were British. What
could they do to stop this? Um really, I
think that what they need to do is they
need to they probably need to have some
level of control of like, give me a
second, my my stream thing is crashing
again. Uh yeah, why is this even
happening? Uh cancel.
>> Uh like yeah, my my stream is just it's
just crashing out today. Like I don't
really even know why. My point is that
uh I don't know whether they're British
or not or anything else. So
uh kill switch on the airplanes. I do
think that, you know, I'm surprised that
airplanes don't have a manual override
where it automatically just like stops
the pilot from flying the airplane.
Like I I I do feel I I'm actually really
shocked that they don't have that that
like you know, okay, let's say somebody
is like, you know, like taking over the
airplane. There is Well, then how did
that happen? We don't want that. I don't
know. I feel like that's definitely a
lot safer, right? I mean, like, yeah,
like I don't know. Like, they do. I
mean, maybe, right? There has to Yeah,
like an opposite there. There should be
like some sort of like manual override
or something, right? I mean, I I don't
know. No, we don't want that. That'd be
really bad. Well, I mean, if you had a
manual override that you were able to
do, I mean, I I guess, but like I mean,
couldn't you just do that? It's a
vulnerability. I mean, maybe, but like I
feel like and everything is a
vulnerability. So, people feel more
comfortable like with this being
possible rather than something else. And
this is the So, these are the people
leaving the airplane.
Oh my god.
pilot. [music] They say he's a Indian
nationalist and I'm hope I don't you
know mess up his name too much. Uh Smid
Malar
and he has 10,000 they according to the
post he's got nearly 10,000 hours in the
air. That's a lot of hours.
>> He was credited as averting possible a
terror attack on Tuesday. Um and he was
the first one that alerted the crew and
passengers aboard the plane that he
needed help in the cockpit.
>> Wow.
>> Let's bring back in Mike Koffield, um
our expert that we began this hour with.
Mike, I I just want to reiterate what
Reuters is reporting that this pilot
covered with blood lying on the floor
had clicked open the release on the
cockpit door. A second set of pilots on
board who were due to replace the first
landed the plane. your thoughts on that
pilot who managed to do that despite
being under extraordinary amount of
duress.
>> Holy [__]
>> Yeah, he he he was extraordinary is
going to be a an underwhelming word for
I mean he's beyond that. He's he's
beyond hero. Um and I think too you're
going to find out that the fact that
these other two folks then set in the
cockpit with an airplane that they
really don't know what what the
situation is until they put their feet
on the rudder pedals and they don't
work. Uh-huh. Holy [__] [__] That is
insane.
Oh my god. Look at me. I'm the captain
now. Yeah, that's insane, isn't it? And
I I I don't even know what to say. And
it's an understatement for real. Yeah,
it is. Imagine if pilots aren't immune
to this. Thanks to Saudi Arabia for
letting them land. Well, I mean, yeah,
obviously they're going to let him land.
It kind of goes without saying, sure.
And a pilot that was stabbed on a flight
Dubai with a terrorist co-pilot was able
to release the door on the cockpit. Is
this the guy? They [music]
one uh pilot stopped the other and the
crew member [music] in the along with
the passengers they got gained control
took over and the third pilot was in the
aircraft and managed to take control of
the aircraft take us to
>> there we were passenger very warm
welcome they took everything
like medical steam and food and
whatever. They were very welcoming and
the people were very calm. No history,
no history. And um we're on the way back
to Tel Aiv safe in some apparently.
>> I mean, good for them, right? I mean,
the fact that they were able to save
this guy and do this, this is insane. I
mean, people are going to say it's a
false flag. Well, yeah. They're going to
invent everything.
They're going to make everything like
this into a false flag because they
don't want to admit like a lot of these
people like this is just the reality is
that a lot of these people will always
run defense for what could be perceived.
We don't really know whether this is
true and is this an interview with the
guy
>> when we are up there and if something
>> Wait, this is the this is the captain
from an interview from a year ago.
when we are up there and if something
happens you know who's going to save you
you'll be lucky enough to have a doctor
on board but then if not then they are
trained I'm not saying they they are
trained to do you know surgeries and
stuff but then
>> they can save your life no so
>> it is unfortunate how uh the entire
outlook of people is there
>> towards the crew [snorts]
>> he's complaining people are [__]
Yeah,
>> when when things are going wrong, you
need them when
>> Yep, absolutely. And they needed this
guy. Obviously, I don't want to show
that photo. That's really gory. But, uh,
holy [__] So, the the guy I mean, and
he survived, too, right? I mean, yeah, a
dentist among passengers saved his life.
Is that true? Is that it? Saudi Arabia
and Israel don't have official
diplomatic relations. they allowed them
to land and actually took care of the
passengers, but for now they're refusing
to cooperate with Israel with an
investigation regarding the Omani pilot.
Hopefully that changes soon. I mean, I
think that really you're going to have
like this is really the situation is
that
I I do think that normalized relations
can exist between countries like Syria,
Saudi Arabia, and Israel and Turkey and,
you know, the US. Like, and I'm not
talking about normalized in the same way
that like, you know, you can go from
Oklahoma to Texas, right? but normalized
in the way that we don't have to pretend
like we're enemies, like we don't have
to actively be at war with each other
trying to bomb each other or anything
like that. I think this is possible. And
fundamentally, I feel like we're
entering into a world where we're seeing
that there are two different factions.
There are the people who want to
conserve civilization, and there are the
people who want to destroy it. And
fundamentally people that are trying to
hijack civilian airplanes and fly them
into anywhere. These are people who are
trying to destroy civilization. This
transcends nationality. It transcends
ideology, religion, race, ethnicity, or
anything else. And you have the
destroyers of civilization that are
existing all around the world. You have
the cartels in South America and Central
America. You have Antifa that is here in
America. You have the other terror cells
that we have in America. You have uh all
of the migrants that are invading Europe
in mass numbers and then not
assimilating and destroying property.
And in France, they're burning things
down. Like this is basically what's
happening, right? Is that you're having
a and and then you also have Iran and
Iran's proxies that are destroying
civilization. And then I would say even
Putin, right? Not maybe not Russia
collectively, but Putin is I think
destroying civilization with what he's
doing with with [__] Ukraine, but
even that one's very political. I don't
want to even use that as an example.
Let's use the other ones prior to that
as the stronger examples. These people
are fundamentally at war with
civilization and humanity itself. And it
doesn't matter whether you're living in
Oman. It doesn't matter whether you're
living in Yemen, you're living in Dubai,
you're living in Shanghai, you're living
in London, or you're living in Arkansas.
These people are your enemy. They are
all our collective enemy. And all of
them together are the enemy. And we have
to come together at a certain point and
say these destructive, psychotic,
abusive, insane people need to be
reigned in and controlled worldwide
because what we're seeing now is a scale
of in my opinion societal discord
collapse, institutionalized protected
institutionalized institutionally
protected uh destruction of
organizations. It's too much. It's just
too much. What do all these people have
in common? They hate the West.
They all hate the West. Like that.
That's the one thing they all have in
common. They're not all Muslims. They're
not all brown. Uh they're not all white.
They're not all women. They all
collectively hate the West. That is the
one thing that they all have in